Wilton Historical Society Neighborhoods and Old Houses Collection
Wilton History Room, Wilton Historical Society
- 1. Houses
  - Houses by address and name
    - 83 Grumman Hill Road - Seth Grumman, Sr., house, undated; Built 1840. (Cabinet 2, Folder 824)
    - 75 Honey Hill Road - Elia Godfrey house, undated; Built 1855. (Cabinet 2, Folder 828)
    - 94 Honey Hill Road - Forsyth-Tibbett house, undated; Built 1800. Remodeled 1930. (Cabinet 2, Folder 830)
    - 40 Honey Hill Road - Tanner-Buckley house, undated; Built 1901. (Cabinet 2, Folder 826)
    - Hubbard Road - Wilton Arms, undated; The four files are (a) purchase, (b) housing equipment, (c) construction, and (d) lawsuit. (Cabinet 2, Folder 831a, 831b, 831c, 831d)
    - Huckleberry Hill - Luther K. Bell house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 832)
    - 148 Hulda Hill Road, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 833)
    - 211 Hurlbutt Street - Andrew Jackson house, undated; Built 1890. (Cabinet 2, Folder 866)
    - 126 Hurlbutt Street - Bennett house, undated; Built 1810. (Cabinet 2, Folder 846)
    - 132 Hurlbutt Street - Bennett recreation hall, undated; Built 1890. (Cabinet 2, Folder 848)
    - 158 Hurlbutt Street - Carvutto house, undated; Built 1924 to 1934. (Cabinet 2, Folder 858)
    - 115 Hurlbutt Street - Charles Goeppler house, undated; Built 1885. (Cabinet 2, Folder 842)
    - 152 Hurlbutt Street - David Hermon Van Hoosear house, undated; Built 1840. (Cabinet 2, Folder 854)
    - 175 Hurlbutt Street - Ebenezer Hurlbutt house, undated; Built 1740. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 860)
    - 157 Hurlbutt Street - Hurlbutt Street school house, undated; Built 1834. (Cabinet 2, Folder 856)
    - 245 Hurlbutt Street - John Hurlbutt house, undated; Built circa 1800. (Cabinet 2, Folder 870)
    - 190 Hurlbutt Street - Ketchum-Knapp house, undated; Built 1739 to 1742. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 864)
    - 138 Hurlbutt Street - Morehouse-Holmes house, undated; Built 1820. (Cabinet 2, Folder 850)
    - 142 Hurlbutt Street - Morehouse-Holmes house, undated; Built 1810. (Cabinet 2, Folder 852)
    - 275 Hurlbutt Street - Platt Raymond house, undated; Built circa 1799. Remodeled circa 1890. (Cabinet 2, Folder 874)
    - 257 Hurlbutt Street - Raymond-Ambler house, undated; Built circa 1805. Remodeled circa 1887. (Cabinet 2, Folder 872)
    - 90 Hurlbutt Street - Rosenbaum house, "Lakeland Farm", undated; Built circa 1910. (Cabinet 2, Folder 840)
    - 436 Hurlbutt Street - Samuel Sturges house, undated; Built circa 1760. (Cabinet 2, Folder 880)
    - 379 Hurlbutt Street - Sheffield house, undated; Remodeled 1940. (Cabinet 2, Folder 876)
    - 187 Hurlbutt Street - Van Hoosear barn, undated; Built 1850. Remodeled 1935. (Cabinet 2, Folder 862)
    - 199 Hurlbutt Street - Wilcek house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 865)
    - 123 Hurlbutt Street - William Abbott house, undated; Built 1877. (Cabinet 2, Folder 844)
    - 77 Hurlbutt Street - William Stewart house, undated; See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 834)
    - 7 Kensett Drive - Isabel Rock house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 881a)
    - 58 Langner Lane - Langner house, undated; Built 1965. (Cabinet 2, Folder 881b)
    - 26 Lover's Lane - Gregory-Merwin house, undated; Built 1750. Remodeled 1820. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 888)
    - 19 Lovers Lane - Hickox-Gregory-Olmstead house, undated; Built circa 1748. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 886)
    - 10 Lover's Lane - Merwin Mill tenant house, undated; Built 1820. Remodeled 1953. (Cabinet 2, Folder 882)
    - 33 Lover's Lane - Wilton Academy, undated; Built 1867. (Cabinet 2, Folder 890)
    - 15 Lover's Lane - Wilton Playshop, undated; Built 1870. (Cabinet 2, Folder 884)
    - 195 Mather Street, undated; Built circa 1790. (Cabinet 2, Folder 894)
    - 74 Mather Street - "Old Stone House", undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 892)
    - 80 Middlebrook Farm Road - Healing house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 896)
    - 24 Millstone Road - Bald Hill school house, undated; Built 1870. Remodeled 1937. (Cabinet 2, Folder 902)
    - 131 Millstone Road - Belden Scott house, undated; Built 1790. (Cabinet 2, Folder 908)
    - 208 Millstone Road - Campbell-Avellar house, undated; Built 1912. (Cabinet 2, Folder 911)
    - 3 Millstone Road - Chauncey Keeler house and store, undated; Built circa 1820. (Cabinet 2, Folder 900)
    - 296 Millstone Road - Daniel Whitlock house, undated; Built circa 1758. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 930a)
    - 221 Millstone Road - Dave Brubeck house, undated; Built 1963. (Cabinet 2, Folder 912)
    - 52 Millstone Road - Holman-Fett house, undated; Built 1932. Remodeled 1952. (Cabinet 2, Folder 904)
    - 154 Millstone Road - Keeler-Seymour house, undated; Built circa 1870. (Cabinet 2, Folder 909)
    - 279 Millstone Road - Nathan Tuttle house, undated; Built circa 1772. (Cabinet 2, Folder 920)
    - 201 Millstone Road - Thomas Herbert Smith saw mill and house, undated; Built circa 1905. (Cabinet 2, Folder 910)
    - 240 Millstone Road - Tito farm, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 914)
    - 121 Millstone Road - William Scott house, undated; Built 1800. Remodeled 1930. (Cabinet 2, Folder 906)
    - 12 Mollbrook Drive - Ely Raymond house, undated; Built 1915. (Cabinet 2, Folder 930b)
    - 175 Mountain Road - Lyman Keeler house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 931)
    - 12 New Canaan Road - Jemmy James house, undated; Built 1800. Remodeled 1930. (Cabinet 2, Folder 932)
    - 5, 9 New Street - Ericson house, undated; Built 1913. (Cabinet 2, Folder 934)
    - 49 New Street - Gilbert and Bennett School, undated; Built 1915. (Cabinet 2, Folder 938)
    - 34 New Street - Harry Lindstrom house, undated; Built 1925. (Cabinet 2, Folder 936)
    - 341 Newtown Turnpike - Henry Finch house, undated; Built 1842. (Cabinet 2, Folder 942)
    - 340 Newtown Turnpike - Kalesky house, undated; Built 1910. (Cabinet 2, Folder 940)
    - 457 Newtown Turnpike - Munson Sturges house, undated; Built 1880. Remodeled 1940. (Cabinet 2, Folder 944)
    - 269 Nod Hill Road, undated; Built circa 1815. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 959b)
    - 441 Nod Hill Road, undated; Built circa 1930. (Cabinet 2, Folder 982)
    - 597 Nod Hill Road - Anna Olmstead house, undated; Built circa 1825. (Cabinet 2, Folder 996)
    - 88 Nod Hill Road - Barrett-Colonel Pope house, undated; Built 1835. (Cabinet 2, Folder 952)
    - 61 Nod Hill Road - Betts-Barrett tenant house, undated; Built 1830. Remodeled 1930. (Cabinet 2, Folder 950)
    - 41 Nod Hill Road - Betts-Comstock tenant house, undated; Built 1825. Remodeled 1954. (Cabinet 2, Folder 948)
    - 262 Nod Hill Road - Blow-Throckmorton house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 959a)
    - 77 Nod Hill Road - Cave-Agnew house, undated; Built circa 1940. (Cabinet 2, Folder 951)
    - 668 Nod Hill Road - Geffen-Geer house, undated; Built 1880. Remodeled 1930. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1004)
    - 141 Nod Hill Road - George Morgan house, undated; Built 1835. (Cabinet 2, Folder 954)
    - 735 Nod Hill Road - J. Alden Weir farm, undated; See Also 1 Nod Hill, Ridgefield. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1008)
    - 1 Nod Hill Road - J. Alden Weir house, undated; Located in Ridgefield. (Cabinet 2, Folder 946)
    - 289 Nod Hill Road - James Morgan house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 960)
    - 634 Nod Hill Road - Jones house, undated; Built 1903. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1000)
    - 651 Nod Hill Road - Leary-Slaughter house, undated; Built 1943. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1002)
    - 209 Nod Hill Road - Lockwood-Cause house, undated; Built 1800. (Cabinet 2, Folder 958)
    - 351 Nod Hill Road - Manuelli house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 973)
    - 610 Nod Hill Road - Mathias Comstock house, undated; Built 1820. (Cabinet 2, Folder 998)
    - 15 Nod Hill Road - Middlebrook school house, undated; Built 1860. Remodeled 1871. (Cabinet 2, Folder 947)
    - 464 Nod Hill Road - Nelson Breed house, undated; Built 1810. Remodeled 1837. (Cabinet 2, Folder 985)
    - 407 Nod Hill Road - Nod Hill school house, undated; Built 1876. Remodeled 1835. (Cabinet 2, Folder 975)
    - 573 Nod Hill Road - Olmstead house, undated; Built 1850. Remodeled 1827. (Cabinet 2, Folder 994)
    - 430 Nod Hill Road - Olmstead-Betts house / "Rock House", undated; Built circa 1765. (Cabinet 2, Folder 980)
    - 523 Nod Hill Road - Orrin Jennings house, undated; Built 1875. (Cabinet 2, Folder 992)
    - 200 Nod Hill Road - Resseguie-Olmstead-Erskine house, undated; Built circa 1740. (Cabinet 2, Folder 956)
    - 518 Nod Hill Road - Samuel Dunning Olmstead house, undated; Built circa 1795. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 990)
    - 312, 314 Nod Hill Road - Scribner-St. John house, undated; Built circa 1750. (Cabinet 2, Folder 970)
    - 692 Nod Hill Road - Webb house, undated; Built 1840. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1006)
    - Nod Hill Road - Weir farm, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 945)
    - 71 Old Belden Hill Road - Durand house, undated; Built 1875. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1012)
    - 69 Old Belden Hill Road - G. Gregory farmhouse, undated; Built 1885. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1010)
    - 105 Old Belden Hill Road - Olmstead house, undated; Built 1800. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1014)
    - 67 Old Boston Road - Abijah Adams house, undated; Built 1830. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1022)
    - 3 Old Boston Road - Barlow-Saunders house, undated; Built 1790. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1016)
    - 20 Old Boston Road - Brundage-Miller house, undated; Built 1855. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1020)
    - 12 Old Boston Road - Miller-Rose house, undated; Built 1930. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1018)
    - 49 Old Danbury Road - Betts-Nolan house, undated; Built 1830. Also known as Station Road. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1026)
    - 15 Old Danbury Road - Job Burlock house / Judge Davenport house, undated; Built 1830. Also known as Station Road. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1024)
    - 148 Old Highway - E. Boyd Smith house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1027a)
    - 170 Old Huckleberry Road - West Woods Cottage, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1027b)
    - 96 Old Mill Road - Henry Olmstead house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1029)
    - 11 Old Mill Road - Taylor house, undated; Built 1820. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1028)
    - Old Ridgefield Road - Betts-Schenck house, undated; See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1030)
    - 15 Old Ridgefield Road - Bundy house, undated; Built 1825. Remodeled 1921. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1032)
    - Old Ridgefield Road - Heading house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1031)
    - 77 Old Ridgefield Road - St. Matthew’s Church / Sturges store / Keeler’s store, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1034)
    - Old Ridgefield Road - Thomson house / Wilton Arms, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1033)
    - 202 Old Ridgefield Road - Williams-Gregory house, undated; Possibly an incorrect address; 2 Old Ridgefield Rd.? (Cabinet 2, Folder 1035)
    - 75 Olmstead Hill Road, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1038)
    - 414 Olmstead Hill Road - Charles Partrick house and Cannon Corners, undated; Built circa 1870. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1054)
    - 411 Olmstead Hill Road - Gersham Partrick house, undated; Built circa 1875. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1052)
    - 190 Olmstead Hill Road - James Olmstead house, undated; Built circa 1823. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1044)
    - 77 Olmstead Hill Road - LeGrand Olmstead house, undated; Built circa 1849. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1040)
    - 236 Olmstead Hill Road - Nathan Olmstead house, undated; Built circa 1725. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1048)
    - 122 Olmstead Hill Road, undated; Three files; the third file (Part 3) includes information on the Richard Foster "Round" house. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1042, 1043a, 1043b)
    - 295 Olmstead Hill Road - Van Summern house, undated; Built 1968. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1050)
    - 229 Olmstead Hill Road - Williams house, undated; Built circa 1790. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1046)
    - 23 Own Home Avenue - Luther Gay house, undated; Built 1930. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1056)
    - 2 Pimpewaug Road - Chichester house, undated; Built circa 1790 See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1058)
    - 200 Pimpewaug Road - Miller caretaker house, undated; Built circa 1910. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1064)
    - 51 Pimpewaug Road - William Smith Cole house, undated; Built circa 1830. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1060)
    - 172 Pimpewaug Road - Wing house, undated; Built circa 1915. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1062)
    - 67 Pine Ridge Road - Cousins-Burdick estate, undated; Built 1912. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1066)
    - 21 Pond Road - Barrett-Hull house, undated; Built circa 1825. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1070)
    - 4 Pond Road - Gilbert house, undated; Built 1859. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1068)
    - 66 Portland Avenue - Gilbert and Bennett duplex, undated; Built 1925. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1072)
    - 86 Portland Avenue - Leroy Sturges house, undated; Built circa 1892. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1074)
    - 183 Range Road - Feltham house, undated; Built circa 1860. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1078)
    - 77 Range Road - Turner-Gordon house, undated; Built circa 1840. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1076)
    - 14 Raymond Lane - Spencer estate tenant house, undated; Built 1919. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1080)
    - 27 Redding Road - Louis Miller house, undated; Built circa 1910. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1084)
    - 25 Redding Road - Mary Stanley house, undated; Built 1910. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1082)
    - 208 Ridgefield Road, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1105)
    - 635 Ridgefield Road, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1178)
    - 831 Ridgefield Road, undated; Built circa 1790. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1242)
    - 846 Ridgefield Road, undated; Built circa 1768. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1250)
    - 923 Ridgefield Road - "Red Lion Inn", undated; See also Historic Trees. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1280)
    - 422 Ridgefield Road - Alexander Resseguie house, undated; Built circa 1752. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1140)
    - 823 Ridgefield Road - Bald Hill Methodist Church parsonage, undated; Built circa 1875. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1236)
    - 735 Ridgefield Road - Benjamin Ayers house, undated; Built circa 1792. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1210)
    - 742 Ridgefield Road - Benjamin Keeler house, undated; Built circa 1750. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1220)
    - 274 Ridgefield Road - Betts-Middlebrook house, undated; Built circa 1730. See also 80 Middlebrook Farm Road. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1112)
    - 1083 Ridgefield Road - Burr Davis house, undated; Built circa 1850. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1306)
    - 830 Ridgefield Road - Chauncy Keeler house, undated; Built circa 1825. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1240)
    - 65 Ridgefield Road - Congregational Church parsonage and barns, undated; Built 1832. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1086)
    - 1028 Ridgefield Road - Daniel Comstock house and Hop Meadow, undated; Built circa 1740. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1290)
    - 1053 Ridgefield Road - Davis house, undated; Built circa 1820. Now 10 Fullin Lane. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1302)
    - 1042 Ridgefield Road - Davis-Graham house, undated; Built circa 1814. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1300)
    - 1054 Ridgefield Road - Davis-Tuttle house, undated; Built circa 1840. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1304)
    - 759 Ridgefield Road - Davis-Weitzer house, undated; Built circa 1830. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1222)
    - 108 Ridgefield Road - Deodate Davenport house, undated; Built circa 1791. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1098)
    - 605 Ridgefield Road - DeWitt house, undated; See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1175)
    - 485 Ridgefield Road - Dunning house, undated; Built circa 1850. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1155)
    - 522 Ridgefield Road - Elijah Westcott house, undated; Built circa 1792. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1170)
    - 764 Ridgefield Road - Elisha Northrup house, undated; Built 1843. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1226)
    - 226 Ridgefield Road - George Middlebrook house, undated; Built circa 1825. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1108)
    - 808 Ridgefield Road - Howard-Kasper house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1235)
    - 760 Ridgefield Road - Isaac Abbott house, undated; Built circa 1805. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1224)
    - 67 Ridgefield Road - Isaac Fancher house, undated; Built circa 1826. See also PM - Notices, Auctions. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1088)
    - 384 Ridgefield Road - James Olmstead, Jr., house, undated; Built circa 1768. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1130)
    - 122 Ridgefield Road - Jessup house, undated; Built 1880. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1100)
    - 807 Ridgefield Road - John Parson house, undated; Built circa 1750 to 1760. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1234)
    - 500 Ridgefield Road - Josiah Lockwood house, undated; Built circa 1860. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1157)
    - 826 Ridgefield Road - Keeler-St. John house, undated; Built circa 1825. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1238)
    - 652 Ridgefield Road - L. W. Keeler house, undated; Built circa 1774. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1180)
    - 860 Ridgefield Road - Lewis Morgan house, undated; Built circa 1770. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1260)
    - 433 Ridgefield Road - Major Samuel Comstock house, undated; Built circa 1760. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1150)
    - 766 Ridgefield Road - Martin-Degener estate, undated; Built circa 1922. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1228)
    - 418 Ridgefield Road - Middlebrook General Store, undated; Built circa 1850. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1138)
    - 993 Ridgefield Road - Middlebrook grain house, undated; Built 1923. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1285)
    - 242 Ridgefield Road - Middlebrook house, undated; See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1110)
    - 879 Ridgefield Road - Millikan house, undated; Built circa 1827. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1270)
    - 77 Ridgefield Road - Nathan Comstock house / Dana house, undated; Built circa 1835. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1094)
    - 1090 Ridgefield Road - Northrup-Scott house, undated; Built circa 1760. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1310)
    - 69 Ridgefield Road - Old town hall, undated; Built 1832. See also Wilton Garden Club records in Organizations Register under Old Town Hall. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1090)
    - 728 Ridgefield Road - R. Morgan house, "Hessians Rest", undated; Built circa 1867. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1200)
    - 358 Ridgefield Road - Rockwell-Keeler-Sherwood house, undated; Built circa 1709. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1120)
    - 782 Ridgefield Road - Ruscoe-Gray house, undated; Built circa 1840. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1230)
    - 550 Ridgefield Road - Samuel Keeler house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1172)
    - 300 Ridgefield Road - Samuel Middlebrook house, undated; Built 1830. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1114)
    - 512 Ridgefield Road - Samuel Middlebrook house, undated; Built circa 1800. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1160)
    - 789 Ridgefield Road - Seymour house, undated; Built circa 1837. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1232)
    - 390 Ridgefield Road - Sterling-Yates house barn, undated; Built circa 1870. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1134)
    - 871 Ridgefield Road - Thomas Seymour house, undated; Built circa 1830. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1265)
    - 183 Ridgefield Road - Turner-Schlichting house, undated; Built circa 1854. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1102)
    - 203 Ridgefield Road - William A. Sturges house, undated; Built 1855. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1104)
    - 211 Ridgefield Road - Wilton Academy, undated; Built circa 1820. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1106)
    - 211 Ridgefield Road - Wilton Academy - Research by Mark Hull, undated; Built 1993. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1107)
    - 70 Ridgefield Road - Wilton Congregational Church and barns, Rings End building, and parish house, undated; Built 1790. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1092)
    - 80 Ridgefield Road - Winton house, undated; Built circa 1925. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1096)
    - 716 Ridgefield Road - Zalmon Morgan house, "Cold Spring Farm", undated; Built circa 1750. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1190)
    - 114 Ruscoe Road - Michael Middlebrook house, undated; Built circa 1770. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1320)
    - 6 Ruscoe Road - Ruscoe house, undated; Built 1826. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1315)
    - 59 Ruscoe Road - Ruscoe house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1317)
    - 10 Scribner Hill Road, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1325)
    - 125 Scribner Hill Road - Jacob Scribner house, undated; Built 1859. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1340)
    - 103 Scribner Hill Road - Samuel Betts house, undated; Built circa 1771. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1330)
    - 45 Seeley Road - Frank Cole house, undated; Built circa 1852. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1360)
    - 105 Seeley Road - Hickock house, undated; Built circa 1759. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1364)
    - 36 Seeley Road - Hurlbutt house, undated; Built circa 1780. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1350)
    - 67 Seeley Road - Rounds house, undated; Built circa 1850. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1362)
    - Seir Hill Road - Deacon Jesse St. John house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1367)
    - Seir Hill Road - George W. Adams homestead, undated; Located in Norwalk. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1366)
    - 76 Seir Hill Road - James house, undated; Built circa 1875. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1368)
    - 30 Shadow Lane - "Whitherton" house, undated; Built 1938. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1370)
    - 51 Shadow Lane - Ebenezer Abbott house, undated; Built circa 1740. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1372)
    - 121 Sharp Hill Road, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1378)
    - 221 Sharp Hill Road, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1385)
    - 186 Sharp Hill Road - “Sharp Hill Witch” house, undated; Built circa 1833. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1380)
    - 203 Sharp Hill Road - Bedient house, undated; Built circa 1815. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1384)
    - 36 Sharp Hill Road - Bryant-Nichols house, undated; Built circa 1800. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1374)
    - 190 Sharp Hill Road - David Bedient house, undated; Built circa 1815. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1382)
    - 224 Sharp Hill Road - George Benjamin Gilbert house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1386)
    - 240 Sharp Hill Road - Michael Abbott house, undated; Built circa 1800. See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1390)
    - 103 Sharp Hill Road - Spencer estate, undated; Built 1932. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1376)
    - 230 Sharp Hill Road - Weir barn, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1388)
    - 179 Silver Spring Road - Thaddeus Scott house, undated; Built circa 1860. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1410)
    - Silvermine Road - Dommick house, undated; Built 1938. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1400)
    - 137 Sturges Ridge Road - Coley house, undated; Built circa 1848. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1424)
    - 214 Sturges Ridge Road - Dusberg house, undated (Cabinet 2, Folder 1426)
    - 88 Sturges Ridge Road - Jabel Sturges house, undated; Built circa 1786 to 1795. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1420)
    - 109 Sturges Ridge Road - Levi Coley-Samuel Belden house, undated; Built 1832. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1422)
    - 21 Trails End - Von Kleydorff house, undated; Built 1913. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1427)
    - Turner Ridge - Robert Read house, undated; Built circa 1951. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1430)
    - 43 Twin Oak Drive, undated; Built 1956. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1428)
    - 19 Valeview Road - Oweley-Altsheler house, undated; Built 1938. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1431)
    - 60 Vista Road - Thaddeus Morgan house, undated; Built circa 1850. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1432)
    - 11 Wampum Hill - James Sturges house, undated; See also PHO. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1434)
    - 31 West Church Street - Bouton Funeral Home, undated; Built 1912. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1436)
    - 38 West Meadow Road - Anson Brown house, undated; Built circa 1930. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1440)
    - 105 West Meadow Road - Anson Brown house, undated; Built 1930. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1442)
    - 136 West Meadow Road - Marshall-Schwill house, undated; Built circa 1930. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1446)
    - 133 West Meadow Road - Morgan-Gray house, undated; Built circa 1929. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1444)
    - 21 West Meadow Road - Scott-Markatos house, undated; Built circa 1930. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1438)
    - 263 Westport Road - Aaron Platt house, undated; Built circa 1822. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1466)
    - 163 Westport Road - Baldwin-Downes house, undated; Built before 1855. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1456)
    - 180 Westport Road - George Green house, undated; Built after 1867. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1458)
    - 191 Westport Road - Green-Gilbert house, undated; Built circa 1880. (Cabinet 2, Folder 1464)